https://www.aclubwear.com/privacy-policy.html

US Dollar $
Wish List (0)
My Account
Register
Login
0 item(s) - $0.00
Your shopping cart is empty!
Privacy Policy
We know that you care how information about you is used and what we
do with your personal information. We appreciate your trust and want you
to feel confident in our services and security as it relates to your
personal information. This notice describes our Privacy Statement. By
visiting our website you are accepting the practices described in this
Privacy Statement.What Personal Information Does This Website Gather?The
information we learn from customers helps us personalize and
continually improve your shopping experience at our website. Here are
the types of information we gather.Information You Give Us:We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way.You
can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not
be able to take full advantage of many of our many features.We
use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to
your requests, fulfilling orders, customizing future shopping for you,
improving our store features, and communication with you.Automatic Information:We
receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact
with our website. For example, like many web sites, we sometimes use
"cookies", and we obtain certain types of information when your Web
browser accesses our website.E-mail Communications:To
help us make e-mails more productive to improve our services, and your
shopping experience, we sometimes send you newsletters of our products
and services, notifications of changes to our policies, and order
confirmations. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, other than
order notifications and receipts, please adjust your "Subscription"
preferences by logging into your account.What About Cookies?Cookies
are alphanumeric identifier text files that we transfer to your
computers hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to
recognize your browser and to provide features such as storage of items
in your Shopping Cart between visits.Will my Information be Shared With Others?We
respect your privacy and appreciate your business. At no time do we
ever provide your account information, contact information, or payment
information to any third party vendor, associate or service provider
unless absolutely necessary in order to complete your transaction and
order.How Secure Is My Information?We
work diligently to protect the security of your information during
transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which
encrypts information you provide to us for purchasing of our products or
services. This website uses 256-bit Secure Sockets Layer encryption
which is the highest level possible for SSL. It is important for you to
protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your
computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer by
clicking the "log off" link.Which Information Can I Access?We
give you access to a broad range of information about your account and
your interactions with us for the limited purpose of viewing and, in
certain cases, updating that information.Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions.If
you choose to visit our website, your visit and any dispute over
privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including
limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and interpretation,
construction, effect and enforce-ability of this agreement shall be
governed by International Law, and you agree to submit to the
jurisdiction/courts of our choice for the determination of disputes.If you have any concern about privacy of your personal information as
used and collected within our website, please Contact US and send us a
thorough description of any issue, and we will try to resolve it.Our
business changes constantly, and our Privacy Statement, and our
Conditions of Use will change from time to time as well. We may e-mail
periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have
instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to
see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice
applies to all information that we have about you and your account.We
stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially
change our policies and practices to make them less protective of
customer information collected in the past without the consent of
affected customers.Information You Give Us.You
provide most such information when you search, buy, order, post
reviews, or other methods of communication via our website or email to
us. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such
information as your name, address, and phone numbers, and email
address(es).Automatic Information.For
security purposes we sometime collects and analyzes the Internet
protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, and
to our website. This is done for your protection for tracking purposes
in the unfortunate event that someone gains access to your personal or
financial information and opens an account, or makes purchases under
your name.Questions?Questions
regarding our Conditions of Use, Privacy Statement, or other policy
related material can be directed to our support staff.
